[
	{
		"options": [
			"KRINKELS",
			"KRONKELS",
			"KRUNKELS"
		],
		"question": "WHOS THE CREATOR OF THE MADNESS COMBAT SERIES?",
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"options": [
			"JEBUS",
			"JEBEDIAH",
			"GOD"
		],
		"question": "WHATS JEBUS FIRST NAME?",
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"options": [
			"DEIMOS",
			"DEIMOS",
			"DEIMOS"
		],
		"question": "WHOS THE BEST MC CHARACTER?",
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"options": [
			"TRICKY", 
			"MAG AGENT", 
			"ATP ENGINEER"
		],
		"question": "WHO KILLED DEIMOS?",
		"answer":2
	},
	{
		"options": [
			"2005", 
			"2003", 
			"2002"
		],
		"question": "THE YEAR OF THE FIRST MADNESS COMBAT EPISODE WAS?",
		"answer":2
	},
	{
		"options": [
			"JEBUS", 
			"TRICKY", 
			"AUDITOR"
		],
		"question": "WHOS HANK NEMESIS?",
		"answer":1
	},
	{
		"options": [
			"BLACK", 
			"RED", 
			"WHITE"
		],
		"question": "WHATS THE COLOR OF TRICKY THIRD TRANSFORMATION?",
		"answer":2
	},
	{
		"options": [
			"7", 
			"5", 
			"10"
		],
		"question": "HOW MANY TIMES DID HANK DIE IN THE MC SERIES?",
		"answer":0
	},
	{
		"options": [
			"APOTHEOSIS", 
			"DESPACITO", 
			"CHICKEN DANCE"
		],
		"question": "WHATS TRICKY FAVOURITE SONG?",
		"answer":2
	},
	{
		"options": [
			"NEVADA", 
			"MEXICO", 
			"CANADA"
		],
		"question": "WHERE DOES MADNESS COMBAT TOOK PLACE IN?",
		"answer":0
	},
	{
		"options": [
			"101011100", 
			"100111100", 
			"KILL ME"
		],
		"question": "WHATS THE BINARY SEQUENCE IN JEBUS SWORD?",
		"answer":1
	}
	
	
]